// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q018: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Approval for small business loans from Grape Street Bank has been ------ faster than it used to be.',
      choices: ['very', 'much', 'such', 'so'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['much'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題171-180/#q171',
    },
    {
      question: 'Ms. Gupta plans to meet with a ------ from the South Bayside Inn at the International Tourism Conference next month.',
      choices: ['representation', 'representative', 'represent', 'representatively'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['representative'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題171-180/#q172',
    },
    {
      question: 'To ------ a parking permit, employees need to submit a designated application to Ms. Reston by the end of the month.',
      choices: ['intend', 'boost', 'remind', 'obtain'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['obtain'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題171-180/#q173',
    },
    {
      question: '------, Ms. Lawrence was unable to catch her scheduled flight due to a lengthy meeting at the headquarters.',
      choices: ['Thoroughly', 'Traditionally', 'Unfortunately', 'Promptly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Unfortunately'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題171-180/#q174',
    },
    {
      question: 'The parking lot is ------ monitored by security cameras 24 hours a day to prevent theft and accidents.',
      choices: ['continuing', 'continuous', 'continuously', 'continue'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['continuously'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題171-180/#q175',
    },
    {
      question: 'If you would like to ------ your reservation, please visit Travel First Group’s reservation site.',
      choices: ['distribute', 'confirm', 'contribute', 'host'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['confirm'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題171-180/#q176',
    },
    {
      question: 'This intensive 5-day course on enhancing productivity will surely help you ------ the efficiency of your daily operations.',
      choices: ['improving', 'improve', 'improved', 'improves'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['improve'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題171-180/#q177',
    },
    {
      question: '------ the training period at the headquarters is over, new employees will be assigned to their place of work.',
      choices: ['Consequently', 'Once', 'Afterward', 'Among'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Once'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題171-180/#q178',
    },
    {
      question: 'Somerville Furniture has been in business for over 20 years and has ------ increased sales each year.',
      choices: ['consistent', 'consistency', 'consistencies', 'consistently'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['consistently'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題171-180/#q179',
    },
    {
      question: 'Daily tours of the chocolate factory ------ at 9:00 a.m. in the waiting area next to the reception desk at the main gate.',
      choices: ['commence', 'commences', 'to commence', 'commencing'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['commence'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題171-180/#q180',
    },
  ],
}